On that stage, I was hurt at times,
Unfair voices cut deep inside.
But I was watching, I still recall,
Smiles of friends and regrets that stay with me all.
Here, there’s nothing but happiness,
Like a table set with love.
Every smile, every tear turns to light,
This place is our true stage of life.
I’ve seen the bottom, I’ve climbed back again,
With certain love, with uncertain days ahead.
Even through detours, I carry hope inside,
And in that moment, the future shines with light.
Here, there’s nothing but happiness,
Like a table set with love.
Every smile, every tear turns to light,
This place is our true stage of life.
Even without a reply, you were by my side,
The mocked and troubled days shaped this life.
So I’ll say it again, as many times as it takes:
On our stage, there’s only happiness—don’t you agree?
In this restaurant, nothing but happiness,
Every table tells a story of love.
Through the laughter and the tears we’ve shared,
This restaurant is our true stage of life.
Now I stand once more, with my friends I’ll win,
Though stones are thrown, “What can you do with him?”
The world may run from tomorrow, blind with fear,
But we will keep building a stage that lasts a hundred years.
To connect you all, to a radiant, shining future.
Here, there’s nothing but happiness,
Like a table set with love.
Every smile, every tear turns to light,
This place is our true stage of life.
In this restaurant, nothing but happiness,
Every table tells a story of love.
Through the laughter and the tears we’ve shared,
This restaurant is our true stage of life